I think one of these times I could take
a picture behind me so the last idea I
had to go back and look what it actually
was because I forgot to write it down so
this is Apple number 18 and how to get
an ID out into the world so one of the
issues shoes suck what issues when you
have an idea how do you actually get it
out into the world and the current way
the current system means that I have to
find the funds to get it created myself
then market it then decide is it usable
by people I mean maybe you decide that
before you put the money in during the
port or you're making it but now you
have to actually market it and actually
see people are going to actually use it
actually so having a place where I can
just come to and say hey here's my idea
and it's not just mine everyone's how
can we make this better and what
features am I missing and how can we
crowd fund it that's what we need need a
space to be able to go and create these
and so that's idea number 18 is the
platform which people can collaborate on
making an idea figuring out what the
problem is figuring out what solutions
are in the beginning technological app
and website based solutions and creating
that together what would it look like
what features should have and how to
actually get it out in the world and the
only reason you're going to do that is
if you put something out there people
like yes I want that to exist and I want
to be on that project and then you help
make it be by offering your feedback and
your ideas on what you want it to be so
it comes very naturally as to what those
are but yeah to be able to get your idea
into the world by crowdsourcing how to
make it
dear Apple pity